elope.com 2019-08-26

# elope Privacy Policy

elope, Inc. cares about your privacy. We use safe, secure technology and other privacy protection programs to keep your personal information secure. Our site contains links to other sites. elope is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our website. The creation of the following privacy policy guidelines grow from our fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy and will serve to guide our relationships with our customers.

1.

| 

We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and will only disclose your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy and/or with your explicit consent.  
  
---|---  
  
2.

| 

Third parties are not permitted to sell the information we provide to them, to market directly to you, or to disclose it in any other way without your explicit consent.  
  
3.

| 

We disclose limited personal contact information to verified requests by law enforcement and government officials who conduct criminal investigations, and require a subpoena for additional personal information, in accordance with our Privacy Policy.  
  
4.

| 

We will provide you with notice if our privacy policy changes and an opportunity to reject such changes.  
  
5.

| 

We use cookies for the following purposes: 

  * To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting the Site. For example, we may save your login information so you don't have to sign in every time you visit the site;
  * To help us customize the content and advertisements you see when you visit the Site;
  * To help measure and research the effectiveness of our interactive online content, features, advertisements, and other communications; and
  * To track Site analytics and use, and to improve Site services.

6.

| 

We let you change your personal information so that you can keep it up to date.
